Twisted all my limbs for you
Two of them in knots, and
two of them in loops
Ribbons tied around like a noose
Wonder if I'll ever get it loose
I don't wanna bruise for you
Holding back my words until
my face is blue
I don't really care about your crew
You can tell 'em what you wanted to
Pushin' me
Lovin' me
Pullin' me
Fuckin' me
Crushin' me
Touchin' me...
I'm done, I'm done
Done doing backbends, I break
And I snap, it's
no fun, no fun
Pushed myself into a box,
while you held out a gun
I'm done,
I'm done, I'm done,
Twisting all my bones like screws
Stretching my self worth,
just like you usually do
Caught you like the cold
or a flu
Praying that I'll someday be immune
Got me like a bad tattoo
Always under skin, even when
it gets removed
Never got a chance to undo
Positions that you forced
my way into
Pushin' me
Lovin' me
Pullin' me
Fuckin' me
Crushin' me
Touchin' me...
I'm done, I'm done
Done doing backbends
I break and I snap,
It's
no fun, no fun
Pushed myself into a box,
while you held out a gun
I'm done
I'm done, I'm done,
Pushin' me
Lovin' me
Pullin' me
Fuckin' me
Crushin' me
Touchin' me