When we're out in a crowd
laughing loud
And nobody knows why
When we're lost at a club,
getting drunk
And you give me that smile
Going home in
the back of a car
And your hand touches mine
When we're done making love
And you look up and give
me those eyes
'Cause all of the small
things that you do
Are what remind me why I
fell for you
And when we're apart,
and I'm missing you
I close my eyes and all
I see is you
And the small things you do
When you call me at night
while you're out
Getting high with
your friends
(High with your friends)
Every "hi", every "bye", every "I
love you" you've ever said
(You've ever said)
'Cause all of the small
things that you do
Are what remind me why
I fell for you
And when we're apart,
and I'm missing you
I close my eyes and all I
see is you
And the small things you do
When we're done making love
And you look up and give
me those eyes
'Cause all of the small
things that you do
Are what remind me why
I fell for you
And when we're apart,
and I'm missing you
I close my eyes and all
I see is you
And all I see is you and the
small things you do
All the small things you do