Intro
(by Fontanari, C.)
Left your kisses in the car,
I'm just sittin' in it
Found your jacket at the bar,
now I'm sleepin' in it
I'm a sucker for your heart,
took a bite out of it
Yeah, I can't resist it,
so-so-so delicious
Can't back out, yeah, you've done it now
Hold me in your arms tonight
Until it's hard to see,
till I cannot breathe
Tell me what to sacrifice
'Cause you're a killer,
going in for the kill, yeah
I'm not scared to go,
I'm collateral
Knocked out,
your love will be the death of me
Not scared to go,
it's not rational
Strung out,
I'll trade it for my sanity
I don't wanna give you up,
I don't wanna give you up (I can't)
I'm not scared to go, I'm collateral
Knocked out, love will be the death of me
You can have me a
la carte, no condition to it
I'm the target throw a dart,
yeah, just stick it to it
Took a step into noir,
you're a villain with it
Yeah, mm, guess I'm complicit
Can't back out, yeah, you've done it now
Hold me in your arms tonight
Until it's hard to see,
till I cannot breathe
Tell me what to sacrifice
'Cause you're a killer,
going in for the kill, yeah
I'm not scared to go, I'm collateral
Knocked
out, your love will be the death of me
Not scared to go, it's not rational
Strung out, I'll trade it for my sanity
I don't wanna give you up,
I don't wanna give you up (I can't)
I'm not scared to go, I'm collateral
Knocked out, love will be the death of me
Love will be the death of me